manjaree.com 2018-02-07

# Privacy Policy

At Manjaree.com, we respect your privacy and take protecting it seriously. This Privacy Policy covers our collection, use and disclosure of information we collect through our website and service www.Manjaree.com. The use of information collected through our service shall be limited to the purpose of providing the service for which the Client has engaged Manjaree. 

###  “I Am a Manjaree Customer.” 

Your account information is held in strict confidence.We do not sell or share your information with anyone. We only collect information like your name, email address, mailing address, phone number, and billing information so we can deliver your purchase product at your door step. 

### Links To Other Sites

Our Site includes links to other Web sites whose privacy practices may differ from those of Manjaree. If you submit personal information to any of those sites, your information is governed by their privacy policies. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy policy of any Web site you visit. This privacy policy applies only to information collected by this Web site.

###  Security

The security of your personal information and our clients’ information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information (such as Transaction with us) we encrypt the transmission of that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL).We follow generally accepted standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can contact us. Any kind of your payment details are not stored in our system. However, just to inform that customer protection is a two-way street. When buying on any online venue, caution must always be practiced. One should note the guidelines that should be follow to ensure safe and secure online shopping experience.

### What About Cookies?

We do use cookies to track a number of activities and provide a desirable experience for our customers, and our subscribers. We do link the information we store in cookies to any personal information you submit while on our site.We treat any data that we collect with a cookie with the same high respect that we treat other data about customers and subscribers, and only use it in ways that are consistent with the policies described above. In addition to our own cookies, our third party advertisers may use them to both improve the performance of our service and provide features such as advertising. You can restrict the use of cookies or delete them from your browser at anytime by configuring your browser settings. (Please note that restricting cookies can interfere with some of the functionality of our website.)

### Newsletters

When you sign up for our services, we will send you newsletter(s) or communications regarding products which may be of interest to you. If you no longer wish to receive these communications you can follow the unsubscribe instructions contained in each of the email communications you receive or by contacting us at info@manjaree.in.

### Changes to This Privacy Statement

We may update this privacy statement to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a prominent notice on this Site prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.

### Contact Us

If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at via email at sales@Manjaree.in or click here.
